Hi, this Sean Hobson, and right now we're working with our centers.
One important thing that we want our centers to learn is they're not always going to stand down on the low block and post.
Some point in time, the high post area, which is all this post area up here, is going to be open.
A lot of times in the zone, this whole entire area up here opens up, or sometimes within the motion offense, people vacate this area, and if a post player will step up here, they can get a pass.
Now if you've got a good shooting center that can come up and flash in the high post, get the ball, turn and score.
So what we're going to have Ben show and demonstrate right now is how it looks first of all when you flash to the high post, then when you get the ball in the high post, you want to catch and immediately turn and face the basket to see if you're either going to dump down off a pass or if you're going to shoot the ball.
This is what it looks like to flash to the high post.
Go.
Ball, ball, ball, ball.
Good.
Flash to the high post, now he turns and faces up.
He's either now got the option if he turns and no defenders on him, or if they just close out like this, he can either shoot it, he can drive it, or he can pass to the additional players.
But that's how we effectively flash up to the high post.